无(no comments)
无(no comments)
英语不太好(My English is not good.)
无(no comments)
不知道有什么途径可以和留学生交流，可以推荐一下吗(I’m not sure how to connect with international students. Could you recommend some ways? )
没了(no comments)
希望有更多和留学生交流的机会(I hope there could be more opportunities to interact with international students.)
很少见到，真的有吗(They seem rare. Do they really exist?)(“they” refers to international students)
无(no comments)
无(no comments)
多开展一些留学生活动(Organize more activities for international students.)
希望开设一点校内的收费语言班(I hope the university could offer fee-based language courses.)
希望开设一点校内的收费语言班(I hope the university could offer fee-based language courses.)
no
可能因为专业原因？感觉本人没有在上课的时候见过留学生，只在校园里偶尔碰见，所以没有什么意见(Maybe it’s because of my major? I’ve never seen international students in my classes, only occasionally on campus, so I don’t have any suggestions.)
Very interesting topic.
Very interesting topic.
无(no comments)
无(no comments)
无(no comments)
keep it up
"For fluid cultural interaction, the Chinese would expect you to speak at least at the level of HSK 5/6. Even if they can speak English. Lesser than that, the interaction is often superficial."
"I think is important to understand that the school itself has a very marked limit on the interactions with Chinese students. We both lived in different buildings which makes that in the day to day activities we won't mix, and also the programs are Chinese tought or English tought, meaning that we will choose the programs that are easier for us, making hard to cooperate academically as well unless we choose to go to a class that will be more challenging. "
Intercultural events in school level 
Chinese students are closed and shy. A hard nut to crack. They also luck confidence to use english which they already have.I dont understand why since they jave studued english as a subject in school just like us. 
Publicize cultural activities outise Chinese channels and closed WeChat groups so more people can be informed and attend
"I would like that as an international student, there should not be a barrier to communicating with local students, i hope we can have more a chance to have collaborative event or academic exchange with local students."
无(no comments)
无(no comments)
"from my own experience, sometimes cultural exchange is different with academic collaboration. i feel like have no problems having communication in cultural exchange events, but when it comes to academic collaboration with Chinese students, i feel it's a different thing and i hope there will be more events to practice how to do collaboration in academic with them. Thankyou"
每一次的活动都很不错，虽然我偶尔参加，但的确感觉良好(Every event has been great. Even though I only attend occasionally, I genuinely enjoy them.)
希望多碰到数学留学生(I hope to meet more international students studying mathematics. 
It's really a good platform to improve communication skill  for both chinese and international students.)
None 
I think every country has their language barrier so wherever you live you should learn their language to have better communication. 
We need more opportunities to improve our mental health as we stay focused on academia all time. 
I don’t know how to participate in these collaborations projects or how to be notified 
对本地学生和留学生来说，二者最想从对方身上学到些什么？(What do local students and international students most want to learn from each other?)